Humane Borders records, 2000-2010 MS 471
University of Arizona
- Series I: Media Files, 2000-2010
  - Subseries 1: News clippings, June 1, 2000-December 29, 2009
    - Presidencia de la Rep. Mex, December 13, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 259)
    - Presidencia.gob.mx, December 13, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 260)
    - The Arizona Republic, December 13, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 261)
    - Folha Online, December 13, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 262)
    - La Opinion, December 14, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 263)
    - Rednayarit, December 14, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 264)
    - Milenio, December 14, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 265)
    - Diario de Yucatan, December 14, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 266)
    - El Universal, December 14, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 267)
    - La Jornada, December 14, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 268)
    - Nacional, December 14, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 269)
    - Cronica, December 14, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 270)
    - La Jornada, December 14, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 271)
    - La Prensa, December 14, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 272)
    - La Jornada, December 14, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 273)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 14, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 274)
    - Nacional, December 14, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 275)
    - Milenio, December 14, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 276)
    - Diario Monitor, December 14, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 277)
    - Hispanic Vista Columnists, December 14, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 278)
    - BorderReporter.com, December 15, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 279)
    - Milenio, December 16, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 280)
    - La Jornada, December 16, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 281)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 16, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 282)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 16, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 283)
    - Elporvenir.com, December 17, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 284)
    - Tucson Citizen, December 18, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 285)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 21, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 286)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 21, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 287)
    - Tabasco Hoy, December 25, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 288)
    - Fresno State News, December 26, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 289)
    - MSNBC.com, December 26, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 290)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 26, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 291)
    - Motherjones.com, January 1, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 292)
    - Stanford Social Innovation Review, January 1, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 293)
    - St. Francis Foothills Monthly Newsletter, January 2007 (Box 6, Folder 294)
    - Refugee Writes Quarterly, January 1, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 295)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 2, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 296)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 6, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 297)
    - Big Spring Herald, January 6, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 298)
    - Salon.com, January 7, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 299)
    - Tucson Citizen, January 10, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 300)
    - R. Hoover letter to editor of Arizona Daily Star, January 11, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 301)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 15, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 302)
    - The Runner, January 16, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 303)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 17, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 304)
    - Intermountain Catholic, January 18, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 305)
    - Christian Science Monitor, January 22, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 306)
    - Tucson Citizen, January 24, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 307)
    - Tucson Citizen, January 25, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 308)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 28, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 309)
    - Disciples World, February 2, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 310)
    - Franklin News, February 8, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 311)
    - Tucson Citizen, February 9, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 312)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 9, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 313)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 10, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 314)
    - Tucson Citizen, February 10, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 315)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 11, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 316)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 11, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 317)
    - Tucson Weekly, February 15, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 318)
    - ASU Web Devil, February 15, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 319)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 11, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 320)
    - Tucson Weekly, February 15, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 321)
    - Green Valley News, February 17, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 322)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 19, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 323)
    - Green Valley News, February 19, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 324)
    - Arizona Republic, February 21, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 325)
    - Google News Alert, February 21, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 326)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 22, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 327)
    - El Norte, February 25, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 328)
    - KTAR, February 27, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 329)
    - Hispanic Marketing and Public Relations, February 28, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 330)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 28, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 331)
    - Harmony, March 1, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 332)
    - Tucson Citizen, March 1, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 333)
    - Migration Information Source, March 1, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 334)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 1, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 335)
    - Medios Mugak, March 3, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 336)
    - UMNS, March 5, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 337)
    - John Birch Society (www.jbs.org), March 5, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 338)
    - Arizona Daily Wildcat, March 6, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 339)
    - U.S. CBP, March 12, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 340)
    - Dakota/Lakota Journal, March 16, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 341)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 22, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 342)
    - KTAR, March 23, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 343)
    - Enfoque Latino, March 26, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 344)
    - El Instituto Nacional de Migracion, March 26, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 345)
    - Tucson Citizen, March 26, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 346)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 27, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 347)
    - Dakota/Lakota Journal, March 30, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 348)
    - The Washington Times, March 30, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 349)
    - SignonSanDiego.com, March 31, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 350)
    - Arizona Central, March 31, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 351)
    - WFAA, April 1, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - United Church News, April 1, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - The Seattle Times, April 1, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - TCU Magazine, April 1, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Arizona Republic, April 2, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - MSNBC.com, April 6, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Politiken.dk, April 7, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - New York Times, April 8, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Salon.com, April 10, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - National Review, April 10, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 10, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 10, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Arizona Republic, April 15, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Arizona Republic, April 15, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - El Imparcial, April 20, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - ABClocal.go.com (en Espanol), April 20, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - BBC Mundo, April 20, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 22, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - SvD, April 22, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Press Release, April 24, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 25, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 30, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 30, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 1, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 6, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 6, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 10, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 10, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 10, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 10, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - KVOA Tucson, May 10, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - KOLD, May 10, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 11, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 13, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 13, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - The Daily Review, May 15, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 16, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 16, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - KTAR, May 17, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 17, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 17, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 17, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 18, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 18, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 19, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 19, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 21, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 23, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Tucson Weekly, May 24, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 25, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 25, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 25, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Tucson Weekly (two articles), May 31, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Tucson Weekly, May 31, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 31, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 3, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - KTAR, June 4, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 7, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 8, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 12, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 12, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 13, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 14, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - AZCentral.com, June 17, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - USNews.com, June 17, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 17, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Arizona Republic, June 17, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 18, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 18, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 19, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 20, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 21, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 23, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 24, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 30, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - General Assembly Resolution, www.disciples.org, July 2007 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Lexington (Kentucky) Herald-Leader, July 1, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 5, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 5, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 12, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 12, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Morrison County (Minnesota) Record, July 21, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Imperial Valley Press, July 28, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Morrison County (Minnesota) Record, July 29, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Hispanic News, August 1, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 1, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 1, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - USA Today, August 1, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 3, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Little Falls, August 5, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 6, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Prensa Hispana, August 8, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Arizona Republic, August 9, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - St. Cloud (Minnesota) Times, August 13, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Fishwrap.wordpress.com, August 19, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 19, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 21, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 21, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Fish Wrap, August 26, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 27, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Wfn.org, August 31, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - Free Lance-Star, September 3, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 102)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 6, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 103)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 8, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 104)
    - News Bank, September 9, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 105)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 9, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 106)
    - ABC15.com, September 12, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 107)
    - Casa Grande Valley Newspaper, Inc., September 13, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 108)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 13, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 109)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 14, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 110)
    - Napa Valley Register, September 15, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 111)
    - KOLD.com, September 15, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 112)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 16, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 113)
    - Tucson Citizen (Online Comments), September 17, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 114)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 19, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 115)
    - Isthmus, The Daily Page, September 20, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 116)
    - Chicagotribune.com, September 23, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 117)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 23, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 118)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 24, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 119)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 24, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 120)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 25, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 121)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 25, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 122)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 26, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 123)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 28, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 124)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 29, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 125)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 29. 2007 (Box 7, Folder 126)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 30, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 127)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 30, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 128)
    - Times (United Kingdom), Online, September 30, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 129)
    - Arizona Daily Wildcat, October 1, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 130)
    - Tlaxcala Al-Yazira, October 1, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 131)
    - AZCentral.com, October 5, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 132)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 11, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 133)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 11, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 134)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 11, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 135)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 11, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 136)
    - Sacramento Bee, October 25, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 137)
    - Fox News Arizona, October 26, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 138)
    - Tucson Citizen, October 31, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 139)
    - Arizona Republic, November 6, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 140)
    - El Universal, November 6, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 141)
    - AZCentral.com, November 7, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 142)
    - Bisbee Daily Review, November 8, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 143)
    - ABCNews.com, November 8, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 144)
    - St. Cloud Visitor, November 8, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 145)
    - Tucson Citizen, November 9, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 146)
    - Arizona Daily Star, November 11, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 147)
    - Agoramedia.com, John Shelby Spong, November 14, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 148)
    - Milenio, November 26, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 149)
    - La Jornada, November 26, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 150)
    - Reforma, November 26, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 151)
    - San Antonio Express, November 26, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 152)
    - Milenio, November 27, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 153)
    - La Jornada, November 27, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 154)
    - IBL News, November 27, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 155)
    - Tucson Citizen, November 28, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 156)
    - Yuma Sun, November 28, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 157)
    - Tucson Citizen, November 29, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 158)
    - San Antonio Express, November 30, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 159)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 5, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 160)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 5, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 161)
    - H. Congresso Estado de Sonora - 58 Legislatura, December 6, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 162)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 9, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 163)
    - Tucson Citizen, December 14, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 164)
    - El Diario, December 15, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 165)
    - Tucson Citizen, December 19, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 166)
    - Tucson Citizen, December 19, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 167)
    - AZCentral.com, December 26, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 168)
    - El Universal, December 27, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 169)
    - Reforma, December 27, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 170)
    - Reforma, December 27, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 171)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 8, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 172)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 9, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 173)
    - Tucson Citizen, January 10, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 174)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 13, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 175)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 13, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 176)
    - Waco-Tribune Herald, January 14, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 177)
    - Elarietecaborca, January 15, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 178)
    - Waco Tribune, January 16, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 179)
    - Daily Sentinel, January 16, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 180)
    - Western Star and Waco Tribune Herald, January 28, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 181)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 2, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 182)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 2, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 183)
    - National Geographic, February 2008 (Box 7, Folder 184)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 7, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 185)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 7, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 186)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 23, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 187)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 25, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 188)
    - Week of Compassion, February 28, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 189)
    - Humane Borders Press Release, April 2, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 190)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 6, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 191)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 8, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 192)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 8, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 193)
    - Wall Street Journal, April 3, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 194)
    - Wall Street Journal, April 9, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 195)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 12, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 196)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 12, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 197)
    - Green Valley News, April 15, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 198)
    - Tucson Citizen, April 17, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 199)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 18, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 200)
    - WMI Central, April 18, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 201)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 20, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 202)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 20, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 203)
    - Worldwide Faith News, April 27, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 204)
    - Sierra Vista Herald, April 28, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 205)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 28, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 206)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 28, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 207)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 28, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 208)
    - Disciples World, May 1, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 209)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 4, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 210)
    - San Diego Union-Tribune, May 6, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 211)
    - Terra, May 14, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 212)
    - Edinburgh, Texas, May 15, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 213)
    - Tagesschau.de Ausland, May 15, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 214)
    - Green Valley News, May 16, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 215)
    - East Valley Tribune, May 16, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 216)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 18, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 217)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 20, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 218)
    - Arizona Central, May 20, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 219)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 21, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 220)
    - Grand Junction Free Press, May 21, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 221)
    - Witness for Justice UCC, May 26, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 222)
    - El Financiero, May 27, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 223)
    - El Universal, May 27, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 224)
    - Milenio, May 27, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 225)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 29, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 226)
    - Issue Works in Progress, June 2008 (Box 7, Folder 227)
    - The Arizona Republic, June 2, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 228)
    - The Arizona Republic, June 8, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 229)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 12, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 230)
    - La Cronica, June 14, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 231)
    - Desert Disciple, June 15, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 232)
    - Cronica, June 14, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 233)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 17, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 234)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 17, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 235)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 18, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 236)
    - Tucson Weekly, June 19, 2008-June 25, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 237)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 22, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 238)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 22, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 239)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 23, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 240)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 24, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 241)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 24, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 242)
    - Arizona Daily Star (correction), June 27, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 243)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 27, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 244)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 27, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 245)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 7, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 246)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 9, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 247)
    - Arizona Republic, July 13, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 248)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 13, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 249)
    - Wall Street Journal, July 14, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 250)
    - El Universal, July 14, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 251)
    - Milenio, July 14, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 252)
    - Cronica, July 14, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 253)
    - AZCentral.com, July 18, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 254)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 18, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 255)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 19, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 256)
    - AZCentral.com, July 19, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 257)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 21, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 258)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 21, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 259)
    - Associated Press, July 21, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 260)
    - Tucsoncitizen.com, July 22, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 261)
    - Dailycamera.com, July 22, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 262)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 23, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 263)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 23, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 264)
    - Chicago Sun Times, July 24, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 265)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 24, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 266)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 26, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 267)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 26, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 268)
    - Christian Science Monitor, July 31, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 269)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 5, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 270)
    - Imperial Valley Press, August 5, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 271)
    - KOLD.com, August 5, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 272)
    - Presbyterian Church USA, August 7, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 273)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 11, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 274)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 11, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 275)
    - Arizona Hispana, August 11, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 276)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 12, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 277)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 19, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 278)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 20, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 279)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 28, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 280)
    - Southwest UCC Conference, September 1, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 281)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 2, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 282)
    - Ajo Copper News, September 3, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 283)
    - Narcosphere, September 3, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 284)
    - Indianz.com, September 3, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 285)
    - Watertechonline.com, September 3, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 286)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 3, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 287)
    - Examiner.com, September 4, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 288)
    - AZFamily.com, September 4, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 289)
    - ABC15.com, September 5, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 290)
    - ABQJournal.com, September 4, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 291)
    - Kgun9.com, September 4, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 292)
    - 1480 KPHX, "The Valley’s Progressive Talk,", September 4, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 293)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 4, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 294)
    - Mohavedailynews.com, September 5, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 295)
    - Foxnews.com, September 5, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 296)
    - AZCentral.com, September 5, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 297)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 5, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 298)
    - Conservativedaily.com, September 6, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 299)
    - Stormfront.org (White Power site), September 6, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 300)
    - Minutemanhq.com via Santafenewmexican.com, September 6, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 301)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 6, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 302)
    - Border Wall as Architecture, September 9, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 303)